Conrado Ramos

Instructional Designer

910 S 12th St, Apt F9, Allentown, PA. 18103 | <u>conram.bu@gmail.com</u> | (484) 597 – 6790

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Emerging Instructional Designer with 2 years of experience developing eLearning Solutions for clients contracted through Bloomsburg University's Office of Instructional Technology. Outgoing team player with strong communication skills and a solid foundation in adult learning with development experience. Open to new experiences and opportunities.

EDUCATION

Bloomsburg University
BS in Digital Forensics
Bloomsburg, PA
2013 - 2017

Bloomsburg UniversityMS in Instructional Technology
Bloomsburg, PA
2018 - 2019

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

Instructional Design Intern

Dana Inc.

Summer 2019 Maumee, OH

- Developed eLearning Solutions for Engineering Department
- Acted as Technology Consultant on the purchase of Department equipment and software
- Converted Traditional PowerPoint Training and Instructor Lead Training to Web Based eLearning

Graduate Assistant

Institute of Instructional Technology at the University of Bloomsburg of Pennsylvania Spring, Summer, and Fall 2018 - 2019

Bloomsburg, PA

- Developed eLearning Solutions for Contracted Clients
- Ran projects as Project Lead in charge of multiple individuals
- Acted as Technology Consultant on the purchase of Department equipment
- Converted Traditional PowerPoint Training to Web and Mobile Based Solutions

Graphic Designer

Office of Multicultural Affairs at the University of Bloomsburg of Pennsylvania Fall and Spring 2014 - 2017

Bloomsburg, PA

- Recreated documents and maintained event databases with a variety Microsoft Products
- Designed event flyers, posters, and other graphic designs with a variety of Adobe Products

SKILLS

- Developed Learning Solutions through Mobile Learning, Web Based Learning, and Blended Learning.
- Ability to apply ADDIE and SAM models to Learning Solutions.
- Experience translating Subject Matter Expert content into Learning Solutions.
- Languages: Fluent in English, Proficient in Spanish

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Microsoft Office: Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Visio, and Access
- Adobe: Acrobat, Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Captivate, Dreamweaver, Spark, XD
- Proficient Computer Languages HTML, CSS

- Articulate 360: Storyline, Rise, Replay, Peek
- SnagIt, Camtasia, Vyond, Panopto
- BrightSpace: Learning Management System

CONFERENCES

Pennsylvania Black Conference On Higher Education, Inc.

eLearning Guild: DEVLEARN

eLearning Guild: Learning Solutions

Fall 2016

Fall 2017

Spring 2017